Herz, John H.; Papers ger015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Essayistic writings, poetry, short prose, 1930-2005; 6; 305 file folders
  - "German Government and Politics from the Textbook Author's Viewpoint", 1972 March; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 4)
  - "Germany", 1974; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 5)
  - "Divided Germany: Analysis and Proposals", 1974; Typescripts, mimeographs (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 6)
    Early typescripts.
  - "Détente and Appeasement from a Political Scientist's Vantage-Point", 1975; 1981; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 7)
  - "The Impact of Changing Patterns of International Relations on Divided Nations", 1975; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 8)
  - "Carl Schmitt", 1975 May-1975 June (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 9)
  - "Technik, Ethik und international Beziehungen", 1975 August; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 10)
  - "Korea and Germany as Divided Nations: The Systematic Impact", 1975 November; Reprint (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 11)
  - "Evolution of Western Societies: Divergent Patterns and Pace Setting Solutions", 1976; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 12)
  - "Ostpolitik - Road to Détente?", 1976; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 13)
  - "Technology, Ethics, and International Relations", 1976 Spring; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 14)
  - "Alternative Vorschläge zur Demokratie. Der Nationalsozialismus"; "'Unsterblichkeit' - Gedanken über Glanz und Elend der Sterblichen"; "Legitimität: Läßt sie sich zurückgewinnen?" Three articles reprinted in John H. Herz zum 70. Geburtstag, 1978 (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 15)
  - "Gedanken über Legitimität, Gewalt und die Zukunft des Staates", 1978 (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 16)
  - "Power Politics or Ideology? The Nazi Experience", 1978; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 17)
  - "Normalization in International Relations: Some Observations on the Arab-Israeli Conflict", 1978 Spring; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 18)
  - "Legitimacy: Can We Retrieve It?", 1978 April; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 19)
  - "On Reestablishing Democracy after the Downfall of Authoritarian or Dictatorial Regimes", 1978 July; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 20)
  - "The Rise of the Corporate State and the Demise of Its Legitimacy", 1978 July; Typescript (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 21)
  - "Social Democracy versus Democratic Socialism", 1979; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 22)
  - "World-views and Awareness - Prolegomena to a Science of International Relations", ca. 1979 (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 23)
  - "Nachruf. Hans Morgenthau (1904-1980)", Reprints, typescript (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 24)
  - "The Survival Problem", 1980; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 25)
  - "Weltbild und Bewußtwerdung-vernachlässigte Faktoren beim Studium der Internationalen Beziehungen", 1980 March 15; Reprints, typescript (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 26)
  - "Political Realism Revisited" and "Comment", 1981 June; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 27)
  - "Amerikanische Außenpolitik am Scheideweg", 1981 August 08; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 28)
  - "Amerikanische Außenpolitik im Wandel zwischen Vernunft und Internationalität", 1981; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 29)
  - "Introduction: Methods and Boundaries" (1982). Introduction to From Dictatorship to Democracy, Undated; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 30)
  - "Denazification and Related Policies", 1982 (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 31)
    Reprints from From Dictatorship to Democracy.
  - "Conclusion" (1982). Conclusion to From Dictatorship to Democracy, Undated; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 32)
  - "Foreign Policy and Human Survival", 1982; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 33)
  - "Amerikanische Außenpolitik im Wandel", 1982 May; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 34)
  - "Foreign Policy in the Framework of an Open-Society Bloc", 1982 August; Reprints, typescript (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 35)
  - "Communications", 1983; Photocopy (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 36)
  - "Power Politics and Policies of Survival", 1984; Reprints (Box 11 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 37)
  - "Reflections on Hans Morgenthau's Political Realism", 1984 February; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 1)
  - "Gegen den Strom. Ossip K. Flechtheim zum 75", 1984 March 05 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 2)
    Photocopy, typescripts, correspondence with Peter von Oertzen, 1983-1984.
  - "Power Politics and Politics of Survival", (1985), 1983-1984 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 3)
    Typescripts, correspondence with Vojtech Mastny.
  - "The Open Society and Its Security - A Reply to Candace de Russy's 'Note on the Open - Society' Bloc Debate", 1985 June; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 4)
  - "From Geneva 1935 to Geneva 1985: Roots of my Views on World Affairs", 1986 Spring; Reprint, typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 5)
  - "An Historical Perspective", 1988 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 6)
    Section in book.
  - "Personal Statement for Scarsdale Time Capsule", 1988 August 08; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 7)
  - "An Internationalist's Journey through the Century", 1988/1989; Photocopy (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 8)
  - "Otto Kirchheimer, Leben und Werk", 1989; Reprint (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 9)
  - "Ossip K. Flechtheim zum 80. Geburtstag am 5. März 1989", Reprints (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 10)
  - "Bürde der Vergangenheit oder: Wie die Deutschen mit der Nazi-Hinterlassenschaft fertig wurden", 1990; Reprints, typescripts (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 11)
  - "Looking at Carl Schmitt from the Vantage Point of the 1990s", 1992; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 12)
  - "Political Realism - Can it Survive the Global Survival Threats", 1992 March; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 13)
  - "Some Remarks on and suggestions concerning Readings on Transitional Justice", 1993-1994 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 14)
  - Outline of a book, 1995; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 15)
  - Untitled, 1995 June; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 16)
  - "Sketches for a book never written", 1996 April 23; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 17)
  - "Ossip K. Flechtheim (1909-1998). Wissenschaftler und Aktivist", Reprints, typescripts (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 18)
  - "In memoriam: Ossip K. Flechtheim", 1998 March 13; Clippings, typescript (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 19)
  - "Reflections on My Century", 1998 September 15; Reprints, typescript, correspondence (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 20)
  - "Nachdenken über mein Jahrhundert", 1999 December; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 21)
  - "Weltbild und Bewußtwerdung-vernachlässigte Faktoren beim Studium der Internationalen Beziehungen", 2001; Photocopy (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 22)
  - "Reflections on My Century", 2002 January-2002 March; Reprint (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 23)
  - "Some Observations on Engaging in 'Survival Research'", 2002 April-2002 June; Reprint (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 24)
  - "On Human Survival. Reflections on Survival Research and Survival Policies" (2003), Undated; Typescripts (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 25)
  - "The Security Dilemma in International Relations: Background and Present Problems", 2003; Reprints, typescripts (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 26)
  - Letters to the Editor (New York Times, Aufbau), 6.160 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 27-109)
    - "Unversöhnliche?", 1949 April 07; Clippings (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 27)
    - "Screening German Officials", 1949 May 25; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 28)
    - "Collective Ban Urged", 1950 January 12; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 29)
    - "Our Role in Korea", 1950 August 13; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 30)
    - "China's Legal Status Defined", 1951 May 29; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 31)
    - "MacArthur's Charge", 1951 October 25; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 32)
    - "Ruling on Bonn Pact Stand", 1952 December 23; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 33)
    - "Contradictions in News Noted", 1953 December 27; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 34)
    - "Disservice to President Seen", 1956 January 20; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 35)
    - "A Defense of SLP's Right to Appear on N.Y. Ballot", 1956 October 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 36)
    - "Value of Small Parties", 1956 October 18; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 37)
    - "Postal Rates on Manuscripts", 1958 March 10; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 38)
    - "Legal Aspects of Berlin", 1959 March 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 39)
    - "Cost of Drugs", 1959 December 19; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 40)
    - "Diplomacy Held at Fault", 1962 October 28; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 41)
    - "Der beste Nationalfeiertag", 1963 July 15; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 42)
    - "The Movie 'Gap'", 1964 February 27; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 43)
    - "Die Mörder unter uns?", 1964 June 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 44)
    - "Events in Greece", 1967 October 15; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 45)
    - "Gesamtdeutscher Tanz", 1967 December 09; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 46)
    - "Warum Nixon 'strikte Konstruktionisten' bevorzugt", 1970 May 29; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 47)
    - "Shocked by Calley Defenders", 1971 April 22; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 48)
    - "On Democracy In Greece", 1972 January 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 49)
    - "The Colonels and Their Critics", 1973 February; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 50)
    - "Korean Tinderbox", 1974 April 02; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 51)
    - "Comments on Professor George Schwab's: Carl Schmitt, Political Opportunist?", 1975 May-1975 June; Typescript, clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 52)
    - "Thomas Mann in Princeton", 1976 January 16; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 53)
    - "Mihajlov's 'Crime'", 1976 March 05; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 54)
    - "Seoul: Time to Voice U.S. Disapproval", 1976 March 19; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 55)
    - "Re: Professor Arthur Betz", 1977 February 11; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 56)
    - "Imperiled Mankind", 1977 August 16; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 57)
    - "Of Palestine and International Law", 1977 September 18; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 58)
    - "Of Palestine, Israel And 'Positive Law'", 1977 October 26; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 59)
    - "Bonn Does Begin to Look Like Weimar", 1978 February 08; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 60)
    - "Sport in Argentinien wie im Dritten Reich", 1978 July 28; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 61)
    - "Of Populations That Are Still Exploding", 1978 November 15; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 62)
    - "Zweimal Bravo", 1979 July 20; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 63)
    - "Commuter's Dilemma", 1980 January 17; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 64)
    - "Weht wirklich ein frischer Wind?", 1980 January 25; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 65)
    - "Wen soll man im November wählen?", 1980 June 13; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 66)
    - "Gefährliche Verarmung", 1980 December 19; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 67)
    - "The Right to Disagree", 1982 January 17-1982 January 23; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 68)
    - "Bonn's 'Valiant Effort' Against War Criminals", 1982 January 18; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 69)
    - "'Hysterical' and 'divisive'", 1983 April 07; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 70)
    - "Kampf dem Atomtod!", 1983 June 10; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 71)
    - "Ein Denkmal für Aufbau", 1983 June 17; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 72)
    - "The President's Error on Covert Action", 1983 October 26; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 73)
    - "International Law Bent Beyond Recognition", 1983 November 24; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 74)
    - "George Schultz ist kein 'gereifter Staatsmann'", 1984 January 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 75)
    - "Über den wahren Charakter der Friedensbewegung", 1984 January 13; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 76)
    - "If the Democrats Had a Shadow Cabinet", 1984 July 01; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 77)
    - "Retirees' benefits", 1984 September; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 78)
    - "'Schwarze' statt 'Neger'", 1985 March 29; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 79)
    - "A Blow to the Elderly", 1985 June 09; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 80)
    - "Waldheims Doktordissertation", 1986 July 04; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 81)
    - "Only Path to Survival", 1987 February 27; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 82)
    - "Iran - Contra Hearings May Help to Cleanse Foreign Relations", 1987 June 14; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 83)
    - "Can Gary Hart's Return Improve the Debate?", 1987 December 27; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 84)
    - "U.S. Must Join World In the Rule of Law", 1988 April 23; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 85)
    - "'Argentinisches Tageblatt'", 1989 September 29; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 86)
    - "Bedingte Zustimmung", 1989 December 08; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 87)
    - "Deutsche Grenzen", 1990 March 16; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 88)
    - "Begin foreign language early", 1990 October 19; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 89)
    - "Hauptprojekt des Bleicher-Verlags", 1991 June 21; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 90)
    - Untitled, 1991 October; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 91)
    - "Lowey's 'no' vote to Gulf War was all right", 1992 April 17; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 92)
    - "Exiljuristen in Amerika", 1992 April 24; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 93)
    - "'Family values'", 1992 June 12; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 94)
    - "Remigranten und Politologie", 1992 July 17; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 95)
    - "Third World Population Explosion Demands Western Response", 1993 May 06; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 96)
    - "Black Schools Took Refugee Scholars In", 1994 April 03; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 97)
    - "John H. Herz", 1994 October 14; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 98)
    - "Washington ist nicht Weimar", 1995 August 04; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 99)
    - "Reaiktionen der Leser zu 'Krieg oder Frieden. Israel am Scheideweg?'", 1996 April 12; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 100)
    - "Democrats have abandoned ideals", 1996 August 09; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 101)
    - "Düsseldorf begeht Heine-Jahr", 1997 November 21; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 102)
    - "Failure to pay UN dues inexcusable", 1998 January 23; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 103)
    - "Postwar Contact", 2001 March 15; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 104)
    - "Wandeln anerkennen", 2001 April 12; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 105)
    - "Global warming is a worse threat than terrorists", 2002 October 04; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 106)
    - "Another anti-war reason", 2003 April 03; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 107)
    - "Staatsterror", 2005 March; Clipping (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 108)
    - Unpublished letters to the editor, 1949-2000; Typescripts (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 109)
  - Reviews by Herz of works by others, 6.161 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 110-130)
    - Erwin Albrecht.Das Recht der Revolution, 1935 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 110)
    - William Ballis The legal position of war, 1939 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 111)
    - John Coleman Bennett.Foreign Policy in Christian Perspective; James Eayrs. Right and Wrong in Foreign Policy, 1966 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 112)
    - Fritz Berber.Die völkerrechtspolitische Lage Deutschlands, 1936 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 113)
    - August Berges. "Der gegenwärtige Stand der Lehre vom dolosen Werkzeug in Wissenschaft und Rechtsprechung", 1934 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 114)
    - Julius Binder.Grundlegung zur Rechtsphilosophie, 1935 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 115)
    - Karl Dietrich Bracher.Die Auflösung der Weimarer Republik. Eine Studie zum Problem des Machtverfalls in der Demokratie, 1956 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 116)
    - Randolph L. Braham.The Politics of Genocide, 1981 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 117)
    - Werner Brock.An Introduction to Contemporary German Philosophy; Gustav Störring. Eine kritische Beleuchtung, 1936 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 118)
    - D. W. Brogan.Worlds in Conflict; Draper, Theodore. Abuse of Power, 1968 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 119)
    - James Brown-Scott / Walter H. E. Jaeger.Cases on International Law, 1938 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 120)
    - Bruno Brunello.Sul concetto di una politica come scienza, 1937 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 121)
    - Hans Hermann Burchardt.Kriminalität in Stadt und Land, 1937 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 122)
    - Ernst Otto Czempiel.Das amerikanische Sicherheitssystem 1945-1949, 1967 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 123)
    - Hans Otto deBoor.Die Methode des englischen Rechts und die deutsche Rechtsreform, 1934 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 124)
    - Sebastian DeGrazia.The Political Community, 1949 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 125)
    - Fritz Dennerlein.Berührungspunkte des Sterilisationsgesetzes mit dem Strafrecht, 1935 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 126)
    - Horst Ehmke.Grenzen der Verfassungsänderung, 1955 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 127)
    - Cynthia H. Enloe.The Politics of Polution in A Comparative Perspective, 1976 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 128)
    - Erich Eyck.A History of the Weimar Republic; Walter Z. Laqueur. Young Germany. A History of the German Youth Movement, 1963 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 129)
    - Erwin Feder. "Methodisch-kritische Betrachtung des Adhäsionsprozesses... "; Adolf Hackel. "Error in obiecto und aberration ictus im italienischen Strafrecht", 1935 (Box 12 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 130)
    - Ernst H. Feilchenfeld.International Economic Law of Belligerent Occupation, 1943 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 1)
    - Iring Fetscher.Rousseaus politische Philosophie, 1960 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 2)
    - Ossip K. Flechtheim.Bund und Länder, 1959 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 3)
    - Ossip K. Flechtheim.Fundamentals of Political Science, 1952 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 4)
    - Ossip K. Flechtheim.Hegels Strafrechtstheorie, 1936 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 5)
    - Ossip K. Flechtheim.History and Futurology, 1968 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 6)
    - Ossip K. Flechtheim.Politik als Wissenschaft, 1953 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 7)
    - Jacques Fournier.La Conception nationale-socialiste du droit des gens, 1939 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 8)
    - Annette Baker Fox.The Power of Small States, 1960 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 9)
    - Ernst Fraenkel.Military Occupation and the Rule of Law, 1945 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 10)
    - Friedrich Giese / Eberhard Menzel.Vom deutschen Völkerrechtsdenken der Gegenwart, 1939 (Box 13 (6-Essayistic writings, poetry, short ), Folder 11)